daqri.com 2017-02-09

# Privacy policy - DAQRI

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which DAQRI collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of DAQRI.com and any related websites and all content, products and services offered by DAQRI (which we'll call the "Site"). Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site. By accessing or using our Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

When we refer to ourselves in this policy, each reference is meant to include any service providers, licensors, subsidiaries, affiliates or business partners that we may use in the course of delivering our content, products and services to you. To the extent such service providers have their own privacy policies (such as <http://unity3d.com/company/legal/privacy-policy> and <http://pusher.com/legal/privacy>) the terms of those privacy policies shall also apply to the applicable provider's treatment of your information.

### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so that we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your hardware capabilities, operating system and IP address, as well as certain information about your use of the applications provided to you.

To customize our service for you, we may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer or device.

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you without your permission. In other words, we do not collect information such as your name, address, phone number or email address unless you voluntarily provide it to us—such as when you create an account on our site or purchase something from us.

Except as expressly noted, the Site is not directed to, and we do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under the age of 13. (For services that are targeted to all ages, including those under the age of 13, this Privacy Policy is supplemented by our Enchantium Privacy Policy). If you believe that we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so that we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information.

You can also contact us by email at [info@daqri.com](mailto:info@daqri.com) to request to see the information that we collect.

### HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We may keep data indefinitely, and we may store or process it on computers located in any country where we do business. We may share anonymous information (such as location, application and interactions) with trusted partners in order to provide you with services.

Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how the Site or our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Such information may be used by such companies or by us in, among other things, (1) facilitating the provision of new products, updates, enhancements and other services, (2) improving software, and other products, services and technologies, and (3) providing new products, services or technologies to you and our customers or customers of our licensors.

We also may make both personally identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief that it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief that it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in cases (2), (3), and (4) above, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent we are required or permitted by law to do so.

You acknowledge and agree that we may copy, backup and store data (including personal information and sensitive data that you may upload or otherwise provide in connection with using our services) in the United States, Europe, or other countries or jurisdictions that may have less protective data protection laws than the region in which you are situated (including the European Union), but in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You consent to such collection, transfers and the processing of such data in such countries. You are solely responsible for determining whether any transfer of any personal information complies with applicable data protection or privacy laws before disclosing any such personal information or using our services.

### DATA SECURITY

We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from unauthorized ("hacked") access or human error. We are not responsible for circumvention of any of your privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

### CALIFORNIA RIGHTS

California residents are legally entitled (at no charge and no more than once annually) to request information about how we may have shared your information with others for direct marketing purposes. Some web browsers send "do not track" signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services. In compliance with Section 22575 of the California Business and Professions Code, we disclose to you that the Site will comply with a user's choice to not be tracked, although certain website functionality may be compromised as a result.

### CONTACT

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: 

1201 W 5th St.  
Ste. T800  
Los Angeles, CA 90017

### DATE

This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 7, 2016. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will endeavor to notify you by additional means.
